<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on bAmpli v0.05-04</title><link>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on bAmpli v0.05-04</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What to change?</title><link>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/what-to-change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/what-to-change/</guid><description>What to change? The decision-making of all companies has been solely based on conflict management. The problem starts with the structure of organizations, where information and decision flow through a hierarchical pyramid structure.
The weak point of this approach is that each manager is solely responsible for preventing the propagation of errors, whether in the information coming from the process, or decisions emanated by investors at the top.
THE SUM OF THE LOCAL OPTIMA ALMOST ALWAYS TAKES US AWAY FROM THE GLOBAL GREAT.</description></item><item><title>To what to change?</title><link>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/to-what-to-change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/to-what-to-change/</guid><description>To what to change? Every 30 years, since the invention of Henry Ford&amp;rsquo;s factory process one century ago in 1920, there have been major transformations in process management.
William Deming in the 50&amp;rsquo;s started a revolution in Asian countries with the Statistical Process Control, followed by Just inTime introduced by Toyota, and Total Productive Maintenance created by Seiichi Nakajima.
In the 80&amp;rsquo;s, Eli Goldratt, author of the literary success &amp;ldquo;The Goal&amp;rdquo;, brought Westerners back to the top with the widely used Theory of Constraints.</description></item><item><title>How to change?</title><link>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/how-to-change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bampli.github.io/docs/docs/intro/how-to-change/</guid><description>How to change? To tackle current problems head-on, it is necessary to avoid wasting energy by managing conflicts between competing departments, companies, countries, continents, and so on. How to provide first-class support for long-term trusts, according to Deming&amp;rsquo;s rules?
THIS IS WHAT I CAN DO FOR YOU; HERE&amp;rsquo;S WHAT YOU CAN DO FOR ME.
The challenge of creating a system to explore one bottleneck at a time would be rewarded by kaizen, a huge concentration of efforts in the continuous improvement towards the great global.</description></item></channel></rss>